elgoog.im 2015-12-18

# Terms of Service and Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting elgog.im. By using our Services, you are agreeing to these terms. Please read them carefully.

**Using our Services**  

You must follow any policies made available to you within the Services.  
1)Don’t misuse our Services.  
2)Using our Services does not give you ownership of any intellectual property rights in our Services or the content you access. You may not use content from our Services unless you obtain permission from its owner or are otherwise permitted by law.  
3)Some of our Services allow you to submit content. You retain ownership of any intellectual property rights that you hold in that content. In short, what belongs to you stays yours. 

**Collection of Information  
**We do not collect personally identifiable information.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
**The site uses cookie and tracking technology to gather information such as browser type and operating system, the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.Be noticed that 3rd parties may be placing and reading cookies on the user's browser for the purpose of serving advertisements.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements  
**Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
All cooking and tracking information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site require you to opt in, and allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you follow a hyperlink to another web site, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

**By e-mail:** admin[AT]elgoog.im  
**Via Twitter:** @elgooG 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
